A Guide to the Records of the Clan MacLeod Society USA, 1899-2009
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Electronic Media 1970-2006.
  - Computer Files
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files-incoming 2000 (Box Box 113)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files-outgoing 2000 (Box Box 113)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files-incoming 2001 (Box Box 113)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files-outgoing 2001 (Box Box 113)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (1 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 114)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (2 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 114)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (3 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 114)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (4 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 115)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (5 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 115)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (6 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 115)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (7 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 116)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (8 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 116)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (9 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 116)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (10 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 117)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (11 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 117)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (12 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 117)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (13 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 118)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (14 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 118)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (15 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 118)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (16 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 119)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (17 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 119)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (18 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 119)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (19 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 120)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (20 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 120)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (21 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 120)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files combined (22 of 22) 2002 and 2003 (Box Box 121)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, incoming 2004 (Box Box 121)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, outgoing (1 of 2) 2004 (Box Box 121)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, outgoing (2 of 2) 2004 (Box Box 121)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 1st quarter incoming (1 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 122)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 1st quarter incoming (2 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 122)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 1st quarter outgoing 2005 (Box Box 122)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter incoming 2005 (Box Box 123)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter outgoing 2005 (Box Box 123)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter incoming (1 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 123)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter incoming (2 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 124)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter outgoing (1 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 124)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter outgoing (2 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 124)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 4th quarter incoming (1 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 125)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 4th quarter incoming(1 of 2)(has additional material) 2005 (Box Box 125)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 4th quarter incoming (2 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 125)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 4th quarter outgoing (1 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 126)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 4th quarter outgoing (2 of 2) 2005 (Box Box 126)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 1st quarter incoming 2006 (Box Box 126)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 1st quarter outgoing 2006 (Box Box 126)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter incoming (1 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 127)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter incoming (2 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 127)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter outgoing (1 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 127)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 2nd quarter outgoing (2 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 128)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter incoming (1 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 128)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter incoming (2 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 128)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter outgoing (1 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 129)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, 3rd quarter outgoing (2 of 2) 2006 (Box Box 129)
    - Bound listing of digital files from Associated Clan MacLeod Societies: part three- E-mail files, FTDNA-Combined 2006 (Box Box 129)
    - Digital files (contains explanatory note and 17 CD-ROMs of the files) August 1998 to September 2006 (Box Box 130 (Binder Case))
  - Website
    - Correspondence regarding the Clan MacLeod website (Box-folder 131:1)
    - Are You Online?-Lots of MacLeods Are! (Box-folder 131:2)
    - Clan MacLeod USA website update- Alexandria meeting (Box-folder 131:3)
    - Clan MacLeod Society webpage printouts (Box-folder 131:4)
    - E-Mail addresses (Box-folder 131:5)
    - E-Mail policy for the Associated Clan MacLeod Societies (Box-folder 131:6)
    - JPEG image printout of Chief John MacLeod of MacLeod (Box-folder 131:7)
    - JPEG printout of the Associated Clan MacLeod Societies 40th Celebration (Box-folder 131:8)
  - Film and Video
    - VHS tape: Clan MacLeod World Reunion, Bendigo, Australia April 28-May 2, 1999 (Box Box 132)
    - Film reel: Dr. MacLeod at Clan banquet 1972 (Box Box 132)
  - Microfiche
    - Microfiche records of the Clan MacLeod Society list, Clan MacLeod Society financial information, miscellaneous information, Chemical Bank statements, and First American [Bank] statements 1977-1980; 1970-1979; 1974, 1977; 1969-1979; 1978-1979 (Box Box 133 (Binder Case))
- Artifacts. 1976, 1984
  This series contains items relating to events and members of Clan MacLeod. There are no subseries.
  - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod memorial pledges (leather bound book) 1972 (Box Box 134)
  - Member, Order of the Good Time, Nova Scotia awarded to Laura Margaret MacLeod 1984 (Box Oversize Box 1)